

NUR AZEHA YUSOF

Front-End Developer

EXPERIENCE

WordPress Admin

Ethis Ventures Sdn Bhd

- Deploy and launch website live online and monitor website performance continually.
- Troubleshoot websites problem
- Update and upgrade custom plugins and themes of websites

SEO Web Developer

iMarketing MY

🛗 June 2019 - Aug 2020

- Cheras, Kuala Lumpur
- Tracking, reporting and analyzing website analytics for improvements.
- Recommend changes to website architecture, content, linking & others to improve website
 ranking position and increasing organic traffic of websites.

Junior Web Developer & Designer

RHA Media Sdn Bhd

iii Feb 2017 - May 2019

- Cheras, Kuala Lumpur
- Managed and maintained more than 15 websites and update content regularly.
- Planned, design & develop responsive websites (WordPress), microsites, email newsletters / promotions & landing pages.
- Perform video editing for markerting collaterals such as company profile animation, montage event slideshow.
- Troubleshoots and repairing minor problems on company PCs and other electrical gadgets.

Programmer Internship

Royal University of Agriculture

iii Sept 2016 - Jan 2017

- Phnom Penh, Cambodia
- Developed the first e-learning platform for students
- Involved in teaching basic C++ programming language.

EDUCATION

UniKL Malaysian Institute Information Technology (MIIT)

Diploma in Engineering Technology of Computing

iii Jan 2014 - Jan 2017

Kuala Lumpur

MRSM Batu Pahat

SPM (Science Stream Course)

i Jan 2009 - Dec 2013

Batu Pahat, Johor

ABOUT ME

A passionate front-end developer with 4 years of developing and maintaining experiences.

Adept at handling online server, websites error & troubleshooting various computer problems.

Seeking to enhance my professional skills, capabilities and knowledge in an organization which recognizes the value of hard work and also trusts me with responsibilities and challenges.

SKILLS

Coding

HTML / CSS Javascript PHP VUE JS C++



Design

Illustrator Photoshop After Effects



Other

Microsoft Office ★★★★
WordPress ★★★★
SEO Powersuite ★★★★